https://www.nexcess.net/policies/privacy-policy/

AU
Privacy Policy (“PP”)
Policies
Terms of Service
Service Level Agreement (“SLA”)
Acceptable Use Policy (“AUP”)
Privacy Policy (“PP”)
Effective October 1, 2020
This Privacy Policy explains how Liquid Web, LLC, its brands, subsidiaries, and Affiliates (“Liquid Web”, “we” or “us”) collects, uses, shares and protects personal information. Headquartered in Lansing, Michigan, we provide web hosting solutions including dedicated servers and virtual private servers to our customers (“Services”). Liquid Web has data center locations in Lansing, MI, Phoenix, AZ, and Amsterdam, NL.
Liquid Web respects the privacy of every individual who visits www.liquidweb.com (“Website”) and/or purchases its Services. This Privacy Policy is our commitment to transparency in communicating how Liquid Web collects, uses, and discloses the information that is collected from you, the visitor of its website and/or customer as well as the choices you have with respect to the information.
BY USING OUR SERVICES OR VISITING OUR SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES OR OTHERWISE PROVIDE US WITH YOUR INFORMATION.
SCOPE OF POLICY
This Privacy Policy applies to how we collect, use, and disclose information from the following individuals:
Customers – individuals who register, on their own or on behalf of an entity, to use Liquid Web Services with the creation or administration of a Liquid Web account.
Event/Marketing Participants – individuals who provide their information to Liquid Web when they register for Liquid Web webinars, subscribe to marketing material, participate in surveys or contests, or attend other Liquid Web events.
Website Visitors – individuals who visit Liquid Web’s Website and opt to provide contact information including an email address to receive communications from Liquid Web. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, a Website Visitor does not include an individual who visits a website hosted by Liquid Web but owned and operated by a Liquid Web customer.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to our Customers' website hosted by Liquid Web. Our Customers are responsible for the information they or their end users store in our hosting environment as well as compliance with applicable laws, regulations, and Liquid Web’s terms related to the collection and storage or personal information.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Customers
Liquid Web asks for your account information which includes your name, email address, physical address, phone number, credit card information, and website domain. By voluntarily providing Liquid Web with your account information, you represent that you own and consent to our use of such personal data.
Event/Marketing Participants
Liquid Web may ask for your name, email address, physical address, and phone number. Participation in events, surveys, contents, or subscribing to marketing material is voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this personal data.
Website Visitors
At your option, Liquid Web asks and may collect your name, email address, physical address, and phone number. In addition, we also collect information such as web server logs, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, or other statistical information as part of aggregated data. We use Google Analytics to help us gather statistical information about the visitors to our Website and how they use the Website on an anonymous, aggregate basis. However, we will not associate this data with your
personally identifiable data unless required to do so to cooperate with law enforcement activity or other governmental request or to comply with law. We may use this information to gain a better understanding of the users of our Website, to improve our Website, and to improve our Services. Depending on the type of browser and device that you use, you may have the ability to control the type of information that Google Analytics use. To understand how Google Analytics collects and processes
data, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
Liquid Web uses cookies, beacons, tags, and other tracking technologies to gather demographic information about you, identify your visits to our Website, other interactions with our Website, and personalize your search experience on our Website. We gather information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, browser type, date/time stamp, and store it in log files. See our Cookie Policy, below, for more information.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
Liquid Web uses the information it collects about you in the following ways:
To respond to any requests from you regarding sales and support.
To contact you regarding any agreements or accepted terms that you may have with Liquid Web for the Services.
To provide you with marketing emails, special offers, advertising campaigns, or newsletters.
To provide you with information logs associated with the use of Liquid Web’s Services.
To contact you regarding functionality changes to our Services or Website.
To develop new features and functionality to our Services and Website.
To collect payment and bill for our Services.
To help personalize searches.
To diagnose problems.
To find and prevent fraud.
To register your domain and IP address through ARIN (American Registry for Internet Numbers).
To carry out other purposes as disclosed to you through the Website, or found in terms or an agreement between you and Liquid Web.
Process for other purposes for which we obtain your consent.
HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION
Liquid Web shares the information it collects about you in the following ways:
Third Party Providers - Liquid Web may share your information with third party providers that provide services on our behalf. These companies may assist with marketing support, processing credit card payments, providing sales leads, and customer support. Third party providers may only process personal information pursuant to Liquid Web’s instructions, and in compliance with Privacy Policy and other applicable regulations (e.g. EU-US Privacy Shield framework).
Advertising - Based on cookies and other tracking devices, we may work with advertising companies to display ads that may be of interest to you.
Business Transactions - To provide information to a third party in the event of any disposition of all or any portion of our business (e.g. reorganization, sale, assignment, bankruptcy).
Aggregated or De-identified Data - We may aggregated or otherwise de-identified your personal information. We own such aggregate or de-identified information and may use and share this information with third parties.
As Required by Law or Similar Investigations - To comply with legal obligations (e.g. subpoena) or investigate potential legal violations. Liquid Web may be required to share personal data in response to lawful requests from public authorities including to meet national security and/or law enforcement requirements.
Safety - We may disclose your information to protect and defend the safety of Liquid Web in connection with investigating and preventing fraud or security issues.
Consent - Liquid Web may share your information with your consent.
COOKIE POLICY
LiquidWeb.com
Cookie Name
Domain
Cookie Category
production_cart_sessid
cart.liquidweb.com
Strictly Necessary
Analytics
Cookies are not the only way to track visitors to a website. We may use similar technologies from time to time, like web beacons (sometimes called “tracking pixels” or “clear gifs”). These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enable us to recognize when someone has visited our Websites. These technologies often depend on cookies to function properly, and so disabling cookies may impair their functioning.
Third-Party Cookies. In addition to our own cookies, we collaborate with various third-party service providers who also use cookies to help us optimize our website and understand more about the visitors to our website. For example, we use Google Analytics to provide us with demographic information about our visitors and to help us analyze how people use our website. Our third-party service providers include: AffiliateWP, Bing, CartStack, CloudFlare, Facebook, Google Analytics,
Google TagManager, HotJar, Hubspot, LinkedIn, OptinMonster, Perfect Audience, and Salesforce. To learn more about how these providers use cookies, please click the links above or visit their respective websites to view their privacy policies.
How Can You Disable Cookies and Other Tracking Technology? Most browsers let you remove or reject cookies. To do this, follow the instructions in your browser settings. Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings. For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org and
www.youronlinechoices.com. Some Internet browsers also may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit https://www.allaboutdnt.com.
YOUR CHOICES
You may unsubscribe from receiving promotional or marketing emails from Liquid Web at any time by using the “unsubscribe” link in the email received, or by emailing us at support@liquidweb.com. As outlined in the Section, Information We Collect, you can also control your cookie settings.
With respect to your account information, you may update, correct or delete information that you provided to us by logging into your Liquid Web account or contacting us at support@liquidweb.com.
You are not required to provide all personal information identified in this Policy to use our Website or receive or Services, but certain functionality will not be available if you do not provide personal information. For example, if you do not provide personal information, we may not be able to respond to your request, perform a transaction with you, or provide you with marketing that we believe you would find valuable.
DATA RETENTION AND SECURITY
When Liquid Web no longer has a legitimate business need (e.g. termination of a Customer agreement) to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it.
Liquid Web takes all reasonable steps to protect information received from you from loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and/or destruction. We maintain technical, physical, and administrative safeguards to secure your information, and we use industry standard encryption for your data that is transferred over the internet. Despite its use of encryption, Liquid Web cannot guarantee any method of transmission of information over the internet is 100% secure. If you have
any questions about the security of your personal information, please contact us at privacy@liquidweb.com.
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS
Liquid Web is a US company and stores your information in its data centers in the United States or, in limited cases, in the Netherlands. Liquid Web may transfer your personal information to countries other than the country in which you live. Privacy laws in the locations where we handle your personal information may not be as protective as the privacy laws in your home country.
CHILDREN
Our Website and/or Services is not directed at children and our services are designed for businesses. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children under 13 years of age, and use of our services by children under 13 years of age is forbidden.
THIRD PARTY SITES AND SERVICES
The Website may contain links to other websites and services operated by third parties. These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party. We do not control third party websites, applications or services, and we are not responsible for their actions. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding their collection, use and sharing of your personal information. We encourage you to read their privacy policies to learn more.
NOTICE TO EUROPEAN USERS
The following applies to individuals in the European Economic Area (EEA):
Controller. Liquid Web, LLC is the controller of your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy for purposes of European data protection legislation.
Legal bases for processing. We are required to inform you of the legal bases of our processing of your personal information, which are described in the table below. If you have questions about the legal basis of how we process your personal information, contact us using one of the methods detailed at the end of this Privacy Policy.
Processing Purpose
Legal Basis
To provide the Website and our Services and communicate with you.
You are subject to a contract with us and we need to use your personal information to provide services you have requested or take steps that you request prior to providing services.
To send you marketing communications.
These processing activities constitute our legitimate interests. We consider and balance the potential impact on your rights before we process your personal information for our legitimate interests.
For compliance, fraud prevention, and safety.
We do not use your personal information for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).
For compliance with law.
Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations.
With your consent.
If we expressly ask for your consent prior to processing your information, our processing is based on your consent. Where we rely on your consent you have the right to withdraw it anytime in the manner indicated on the Website.
To share your personal information as described in this Policy.
This sharing constitutes our legitimate interests, and in some cases may be necessary to comply with our legal obligations.
Retention. We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which
we process your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.
Your Rights. European data protection laws give you certain rights regarding your personal information. You may ask us to take the following actions in relation to your personal information that we hold:
Access. Provide you with information about our processing of your personal information and give you access to your personal information.
Correct. Update or correct inaccuracies in your personal information.
Delete. Delete your personal information.
Transfer. Transfer a machine-readable copy of your personal information to you or a third party of your choice
Restrict. Restrict the processing of your personal information.
Object. Object to our reliance on our legitimate interests as the basis of our processing of your personal information that impacts your rights.
You may submit these requests by contacting us as detailed at the end of this Privacy Policy. We may request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and process your request. Applicable law may require or permit us to decline your request. If we decline your request, we will tell you why, subject to legal restrictions. If you would like to submit a complaint about our use of your personal information or response to your requests regarding your personal information, you
may contact us or submit a complaint to the data protection regulator in your jurisdiction. You can find your data protection regulator here.
Cross-Border Data Transfers. Any information you provide to us through the use of the Website may be stored, processed, transferred among, and accessed from the United States and other countries which may not guarantee the same level of protection of personal information as the one in which you reside. However, we will handle your personal information in accordance with this Policy regardless of where your personal information is kept. Regarding transfers from the EEA to the
United States, we rely on the derogations for transfers which are necessary to perform the transaction with you. Where required by law, you may request a copy of the suitable mechanisms we have in place by contacting us as detailed below. If you reside in other non-US jurisdictions outside the EEA, your use of the Website or provision of any personal information constitutes your consent for the transfer of such data to the United States for the purposes identified above. If you have questions
about cross-border transfers, please contact us as detailed below.
NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
The following section applies to California residents.
Shine the Light. Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, you have the right to ask us once a year if we have shared your personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make a request please contact us as instructed in the “How to Contact Us” section below and specify you are making a Shine the Light request.
California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”). The CCPA creates consumer privacy rights and requires businesses to make disclosures about their privacy policies and practices. Pursuant to the CCPA, both our privacy practices and your privacy rights are discussed in detail in the following information.
Personal Information We Collect. We collect your personal information when you interact with our Website or otherwise communicate with us. For the purposes of this Privacy Notice, “personal information” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device. We have collected the following categories of personal information covered by
the CCPA from consumers within the past 12 months, and have used it for the following business purposes:
Category of Personal Information Collected
Business Purpose of Collection
Source(s) of information
Identifiers, including real name, alias, mailing address, email address, account name, telephone numbers, and unique personal identifiers such as online identifiers and IP address
To provide our Site and
Services and to market our
Services to you
Directly from you when you contact us, order Services, set up an account, or respond to promotions as well as through our authorized resellers if you purchase Services through them
Geolocation data
To provide our Services and assist in marketing and identify Website traffic patterns
Passively when you visit our Website
Financial information, including credit card number or debit card number
To fulfill your orders for our Services
Directly from you or from our authorized resellers when you pay for Services
Commercial information, including Services purchased
To fulfill your orders for our Services
Directly from you or from our authorized resellers when you order our Services
Internet or other electronic network activity information, including browsing history, search history, and information regarding an individual’s interaction with an internet site, application, or advertisement
To provide you more relevant content, track original Website visits, and optimize your Website experience as well as to ensure our systems are properly functioning
Passively when you visit our Website
We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible business purposes without providing you notice.
Sharing Your Information. We do not sell your personal information, but may disclose it to third parties for a business purpose. Specifically, in the past 12 months we have disclosed unique personal identifiers such as online identifiers and IP address and Internet or other electronic network activity information to our internet service providers, operating systems and platforms, and marketing intelligence service providers.
Your Rights. The CCPA gives you certain rights regarding your personal information:
Right to Know. You may request no more than twice in a 12-month period that we provide you with copies of specific personal information we have collected, sold, or disclosed about you. However, under California law, we cannot provide you with certain sensitive information, despite your request (for example, we will not send you copies of your social security number even if it is something we collected).
Right to Delete. You may request that we delete certain personal information we have collected about you, with certain exceptions.
Exercising Your Rights. To exercise your rights above, please submit a request to us here, by emailing us at privacy@liquidweb.com, or by calling us at 1-800-580-4985. Please describe your request with sufficient detail so we can properly respond to your request. As part of your request, please specify which right you are exercising and be prepared to provide the
following information: name, email address, and the type of request you wish to make. We may ask for additional information to verify your identity. The information you provide in your request and any follow up information we ask for from you will be used solely to verify your request. After receiving your request, we may need to contact you for further information and will notify you if your request has been granted or declined, or if an exception applies to your request. Only you or an
individual designated as your authorized agent to act on your behalf may make a request related to your personal information. We may not discriminate against you if you choose to exercise your rights.
Responding to Your Rights Request. We will try to respond to your request within 45 days. If we need more time, we will contact you with the reason we need more time and the extension period. We will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option. In response to your request to know, we will only disclose the information we have collected in the 12 months prior to our receipt of your request. Our response will also explain the reasons we cannot comply
with any request, if applicable. We will not charge a fee to process or respond to your request unless your request is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate prior to completing your request.
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
Liquid Web reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, however, should we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the changes, you may terminate your Services.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy, or wish to exercise any of your statutory rights, please contact us at:
Liquid Web, LLC Privacy Matters
c/o Liquid Web, LLC
Attn: Director of Security
2703 Ena Drive
Lansing, MI 48917
USA
Email – privacy@liquidweb.com
We use cookies to understand how you interact with our site, to personalize and streamline your experience, and to tailor advertising. By continuing to use our site, you accept our use of cookies and accept our Privacy Policy.
Accept
